<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="akshan_passive">
        <item>Dirty Fighting</item>
        <item>
            Every three hits from Akshan\'s Attacks and Abilities deals bonus damage and grants him
            a Shield if the target was a champion. When Akshan Attacks, he fires an additional
            Attack for reduced damage. If he cancels the additional Attack, he instead gains Move Speed.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="akshan_first_ability">
        <item>Avengerang</item>
        <item>
            Akshan throws a boomerang that deals damage going out and coming back, extending its
            range each time it hits an enemy.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="akshan_second_ability">
        <item>Going Rogue</item>
        <item>
            Akshan passively marks enemy champions as Scoundrels when they kill his ally champions.
            If Akshan kills a Scoundrel, he resurrects the allies they killed, gains bonus gold, and
            clears all marks. When activated, Akshan enters camouflage and gains Move Speed and
            Mana Regen while moving towards Scoundrels. Akshan loses the camouflage quickly while
            he is not in brush or near terrain.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="akshan_third_ability">
        <item>Heroic Swing</item>
        <item>
            Akshan fires a grappling hook into terrain then swings around it, repeatedly firing at
            the nearest enemy while swinging. He can jump off early or gets knocked off when
            colliding with champions or terrain.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="akshan_fourth_ability">
        <item>Comeuppance</item>
        <item>
            Akshan locks onto an enemy champion and starts storing bullets. When released, he fires
            all stored bullets, dealing damage based on missing health to the first champion,
            minion, or structure hit.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>